http://lakewoodfootball.com/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
Welcome to www.lakewoodfootball.com. If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern COMPANY's relationship with you in relation to this website.The term 'COMPANY' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use: LakewoodFootball.Com is a non-profit website and is in no way affiliated with Lakewood High School.The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without COMPANY's prior written consent.Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States of America.
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how COMPANY uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. COMPANY is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. COMPANY may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st of September, 2010.What We CollectWe may collect the following information: namecontact information including email addressother information relevant to user surveys and/or offersthe information is used solely for internal record keeping
What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better website, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our website.We may periodically send promotional emails about new website updates, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
© 2020
Lucio Arellano | All Rights Reserved. www.lakewoodfootball.com
| Terms of Use
Share by:
